https://www.sccfcu.org/privacy-policy/

Online BankingUser IDPasswordLog InForgot PasswordRegister
HOMECONTACT USLOCATIONSSEARCH THIS SITEAccountsCheckingRewards CheckingATM and Visa Check CardOverdraft ProtectionIdentity TheftSavingsSavingsCertificatesMoney MarketHoliday & Vacation ClubRetirementIRA’SRetirement CentralYouth ProgramsM3 Money Club (ages 12 and under)Get Started (ages 13-19)KIDS ZONEProject LifeFor Young AdultsSmart StartMoving UpLearnBorrowSaveLoans & Credit CardsVehicle LoansCar Buying ServicesPersonal Loans and LinesHome LoansCredit CardsStudent LoansLending ToolsDebt ProtectionGAP – Add’l Auto ProtectionLoan Switch KitSkip a PayServicesOnline ServicesMobile BankingBanking by PhoneMember ServicesMember DiscountsResourcesSecurityWebinarsBlogsFinancial Fitness CenterFinancial CalculatorsInsuranceAD&D InsuranceAuto & Home InsuranceLife InsuranceTurbo TaxVolunteer Income Tax (VITA) ProgramAbout UsWho We AreOur HistoryManagementFinancial StatementPress ReleasesCommunityCommunity EventsCommunity OutreachEducational ScholarshipsTeddy Bears on PatrolMembershipJoin UsRefer a MemberRelationship RewardsCorporate Partner BenefitsCalendarCOVID-19 Info
Home >
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
Rev. March 2018
FACTS
What does Santa Clara County Federal Credit Union and its Affiliate Credit Union Service Organization (CUSO), SCC Financial & Insurance Services, Inc., do with your personal information
Why?
Financial companies choose how they share your personal information. Federal law gives consumers the right to limit some but not all sharing. Federal law also requires us to tell you how we collect, share, and protect your personal information. Please read this notice carefully to understand what we do.
What?
The types of personal information we collect and share depend on the product or service you have with us. This information can include:
Social Security number and date of the birth
Credit history and credit scores
Account balances and payment/transaction history
Assets and Income
How?
All financial companies need to share members’ personal information to run their everyday business. In the section below, we list the reasons financial companies can share their members’ personal information; the reasons Santa Clara County Federal Credit Union and its Affiliate Credit Union Service Organization, SCC Financial & Insurance Services, Inc., chooses to share; and whether you can limit this sharing.
Reasons we can share your personal information
Reasons we can share your personal information
Does Santa Clara County Federal Credit Union and its affiliate CUSO, SCC Financial & Insurance Services, Inc., share?
Can you limit this sharing?
For our everyday business purposes – such as to process your transactions, maintain your account(s), respond to court orders and legal investigations, or report to credit bureaus
Yes
No
For our marketing purposes – to offer our products and services to you
Yes
No
For joint marketing with other financial companies
Yes
Yes
For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes – information about your transactions and experiences
Yes
Yes
For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes – information about your creditworthiness
Yes
Yes
For our affiliates to market to you
Yes
Yes
For nonaffiliates to market to you
Yes
Yes
To limit our sharing
Call 1-408-282-0700 or 1-800-282-6212, or
Mail the form below, or
Bring it in to any County Federal Branch
Please Note:
If you are a new member, we can begin sharing your information 45 days from the date we sent this notice. When you are no longer our member, we continue to share your information as described in the notice. If you have a joint account or joint credit with us, we will treat an opt-out by one of you as an opt-out by all of you. However, you can contact us at any time to limit our sharing.
Questions?
Call 1-408-282-0700 or 1-800-282-6212 or visit www.sccfcu.org
Mail-In Opt-Out Form CLICK HERE TO VIEW AND PRINT THE MAIL-IN OPT-OUT FORM
Who We Are
Who is providing this notice?
Santa Clara County Federal Credit Union and its Affiliate Credit Union Service Organization, SCC Financial & Insurance Services, Inc.
What we do
How does Santa Clara County Federal Credit Union and its Affiliate Credit Union Service Organization, SCC Financial & Insurance Services, Inc., protect my personal information?
To protect your personal information from unauthorized access and use, we use security measures that comply with federal law. These measures include computer safeguards and secured files and buildings.
How does Santa Clara County Federal Credit Union and its Affiliate Credit Union Service Organization, SCC Financial & Insurance Services, Inc., collect my personal information?
We collect your personal information, for example, when you
Open an account
Apply for a loan
Use your credit or debit card
Make deposits or withdrawals from your account
Give us your income information
We also collect your personal information from others, such as credit bureaus, affiliates, or other companies.
Why can’t I limit all sharing?
Federal law gives you the right to limit only
Sharing for affiliates’ everyday business purposes – information about your creditworthiness
Affiliates from using your information to market to you
Sharing for non-affiliates to market to you
State laws and individual companies may give you additional rights to limit sharing. See below for more on your rights under state law.
What happens when I limit sharing for an account I hold jointly with someone else?
Your choice will apply to everyone on your account.
Definitions
Affiliates
Companies related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and non-financial companies.
Our affiliates include financial companies such as Santa Clara County Federal Credit Union and its Credit Union Service Organization, SCC Financial & Insurance Services, Inc.
Non-affiliates
Companies not related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and non-financial companies.
Non-affiliates we share with can include insurance companies.
Joint marketing
A formal agreement between non-affiliated financial companies that together market financial products or services to you.
Our joint marketing partners may include a financial planner, an investment advisor, and companies that sell various types of insurance.
Other Important Information
California residents have the right to limit sharing personal information with other financial institutions to jointly market, and we extend this right to all our members.
Click to Print
Contact Us
Calendar
Locations
Member Discounts
Rates
Apply for a Loan
Become a Member
Online Services
Financial Calculators
Need help with your mortgage?
Online Privacy Notice
Privacy Policy
California Privacy Act
California Consumer Privacy Policy
Disclosures
Copyright © 2020 Santa Clara County Federal Credit Union
Routing Number: 321176972
NMLS# 415778
If you are using a screen reader or other auxiliary aid and having problems using this website, please call 1-800-282-6212 for assistance.
Your savings federally insured to at least $250,000 and backed by the full faith and credit of the United States Government. National Credit Union Administration, a U.S. Government Agency.
TO TOP
